ventones.com 2010-11-04

# Privacy Policy - Ventones

| 

Updated: April, 2009 

This Privacy Policy has been created in order to disclose to you, the user, the information collection, purpose and disclosure for Ventones Inc and the Ventones site (“Site”). We take your privacy seriously. This policy is in addition to the Terms of Service governing the website and should be used in conjunction with them. 

## Collection of Personal Information

In order to download and use Ringtones, Wallpapers and Text Alerts, personally identifiable information is supplied by you. These may include your name, address, mobile number and email address You may request modification of your personal information and registration data by contacting the us at privacypolicy [at] ventones . com Pursuant to the Terms of Use, it is your responsibility to maintain and promptly update the Registration Data to keep it true, accurate, current and complete. 

You are consenting to transfer your personally identifiable information to Ventones in order to contact you electronically in delivering notices related to your use of the Service and the website. 

## Links to Third Party Sites

This website may contain links to other sites. Ventones is not held responsible for the privacy policy of other sites. 

## Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive containing information about use of cookies on website. Cookie acts as alphanumeric identifiers transferring to your computer to enable the system to recognize your browser and to provide features. To enhance the interests and experience of using our website, we may use cookie on it. However, cookies, by themselves do not tell us your personally identifiable information only if you have chosen to provide such information to us when you register at the website. As a customer, your personally identifiable information may be linked to data stored in the cookie. 

## Google and the DoubleClick DART cookie

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.   
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.   
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

## Security Features

We have adopted generally accepted industry standards to protect your security and have put in place procedures to prevent unauthorized access and maintain data security. However, there is always a potential risk involved in the Internet communication for visitors and customers when sending information to Ventones. Therefore, we cannot guarantee absolute security of your personal information. 

Your personal information is protected by a password created upon registration. Ventones will not be held responsible for any unauthorized access of illegal or unauthorized use of information through unauthorized or improper use of your account or membership privileges due to your failure to secure your password. If you have any doubt that your password was compromised , we strongly suggest that you change your password or consult Ventones about this. 

## Notification of Changes to Privacy Policy

Any changes to this Agreement will be notified to all registered users by posting such changes to this Site. Please review this Site on a regular basis, as your continued use of the Site will be deemed acceptance of such changes. If you have further questions, comments or concerns regarding privacy policy, or if you would like to opt-out, please contact us at support [at] ventones . com. 

|
